# AGNIESZKA WÓJCIK

# FRONT-END DEVELOPER



## INTRODUCTION

Hi, I'm Agnieszka. I have over two years of commercial experience as a Junior Front-End Developer. In AC Project I have broadened my knowledge of Javascript and its framework Ember.js, React.js, SASS and code testing. I also learned how to work in a team of several people focused on the delivery of one large project designed for the hotel industry.

By working in Multi-Design Studio I got experience in HTML, SCSS, Photoshop and PHP. It was much smaller team and we worked on several smaller projects for individual customers based on CMS Wordpress.

# **EXPERIENCE**

# JUNIOR FRONT-END DEVELOPER I AC PROJECT

April 2017 - February 2019

The company I was working for created an app for hospitality industry. On daily basis, I wrote front-end code and managed various things related to front-end layer of this application, such as communication with back-end via REST and refactoring the existing code. On a daily basis I was responsible for delivering business functionalities, consulting projects with designers, creating components documentation and writing integration and acceptance tests. Most of the time we were writing an app using Ember.js, but we also had a POC with React.js that lasted three months.

#### FRONT-END DEVELOPER I MULTI DESIGN STUDIO

November 2016 - March 2017

I was responsible for development of front-end layers of websites, creating and maintaining Wordpress based sites and modifying Plugins and Templates. I have advised in the area of website designs creation. Sample websites are available at http://prefkon.pl/ http://redgarden.pl/blog/ http://sw-c.pl/

# **SKILLS**

HTML / CSS / RWD JAVASCRIPT

PHOTOSHOP EMBER.JS

REACT GITHUB / GITLAB

QUNIT DOCKER

REST API JQUERY

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **EMBER COURSE**

AC Project Katowice September 2018

#### JUNIOR FRONT-END DEVELOPER COURSE

ProEdukacja in Katowice July 2016 - September 2016

# SPATIAL ECONOMY

University of Economics in Katowicach October 2012 - October 2015

## CONTACT

#### PHONE I EMAIL

510 - 434 - 786 agnieszka.weronika.wojcik@gmail.com

# WEBSITES

https://github.com/angulawk

https://angulawk.github.io/portfolio/

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ agnieszka-w%C3%B3jcik-445311140/

<sup>&</sup>quot;I hereby consent to processing by the advertiser of my personal data, included in my application documents, for the purposes to implement the recruitment process according to the act of 29 August 1997 on personal data protection (consolidated text: Journal of Laws of 2016, pos. 922). I also consent to processing of my personal data by the advertiser for the purposes of any future recruitment processes."